Guide to the Violet Hunt papers, 1858-1962.
Hunt, Violet papers, 1858-1962.
- Series II. Correspondence
  - 3. To Violet Hunt (by author, then by date)
    - Smyth, Ethel, 1858-1944. -- Jan. 23, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 30-a-b)
    - Smyth, Ethel, 1858-1944. (continued) -- Jan. 23, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 30-a-b)
      Coign, Woking Dear Mrs Hunt. No indeed! I have/seldom forgotten anything
    - Soskice, Juliet Hueffer -- June 22 [1927] (Box 8, Folder 31-a)
      13A, Elsham Road, Kensington, W. Dear Violet I will send you the/chair
    - Soskice, Juliet Hueffer -- June 24 [1927] (Box 8, Folder 31-b)
      13A, Elsham Road, Kensington, W. Dear Violet Thank you for your/letter.
    - Soskice, Juliet Hueffer -- June 30 [1927] (Box 8, Folder 31-c)
      13A, Elsham Road, Kensington, W. Dear Violet With regard to your letter/regarding
    - Spielmann, M. H. (Marion Harry), 1858-1948. -- Dec. 31, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 32)
      Uplands, Folkestone Dear Mrs. Hueffer, I was glad to receive your portrait
    - Steen, Marguerite -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-a)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands My ear Violet Hunt - I'm back to earth
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Saturday [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-b)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands My dear Violet Hunt - What a lovely letter. I didn't dare
    - Steen, Marguerite -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-c)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands My dear Violet Hunt - Bless you for your/little note!
    - Steen, Marguerite -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-d)
    - Steen, Marguerite (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-d)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Violet Hunt - Oh dear. I suppose this/means you won't.
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Saturday [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 33-e)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Violet Hunt Are you thinking I'm a thankless modern,
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Jan. 9 [n.y.] (Box 8, Folder 33-f)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Miss Violet Hunt, Forgive the typewriter - it is all
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Mar. 21 [n.y.] (Box 8, Folder 33-g)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands -- But, dear, dear Violet Hunt, I think more of/your criticism
    - Steen, Marguerite -- July 10 [n.y.] (Box 8, Folder 33-h)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands My dear Violet Hunt - Do you think I have/forgotten you
    - Steen, Marguerite -- July 24 [n.y.] (Box 8, Folder 33-i)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands My dear - Thank you so much for both your letters:
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Jan. 6, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 33-j)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Miss Violet Hunt, I am returning, with many thanks, the/book
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Jan. 12, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 33-k)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Miss Violet Hunt, This is just to tell you - in case you should
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Feb. 4, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 33-l)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Miss Violet Hunt, I wanted to write to you immediately to/say
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Feb. 13, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 33-m)
      Paddocks, Grange-over-Sands Dear Miss Violet Hunt, I am sending you a copy of Stallion
    - Steen, Marguerite -- Mar. 23, 1934 (Box 8, Folder 33-n)
      Halassan, Maru My dear Violet Hunt - No - I'm NOT like that.
      2 ll. + 3
      With newspaper photo [two photcopies] of Marguerite Steen.
    - Stirling, Wilhelmina -- May 25 [n.y.] (Box 8, Folder 34)
      30, Launceston Place, Palace Gate, W.8 Dear Mrs Hueffer, My Richmond book is just in the Press
    - Street, Alice -- Mar. 17 [1924] (Box 8, Folder 35-a)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet I am so sorry I/cannot help you
    - Street, Alice -- Mar. 25, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 35-b)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet I return these interesting/letters
    - Street, Alice (continued) -- Mar. 25, 1924 (Box 8, Folder 35-b)
    - Street, Alice -- Apr. 9, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 35-c)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet I am very sorry/but I fear I cannot
    - Street, Alice -- Apr. 30, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 35-d)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet, I hope these extracts will/be of use to you.
    - Street, Alice -- May 1 [1923] (Box 8, Folder 35-e)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet I sent off my packet to/you
    - Street, Alice -- May 4, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 35-f)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet, I enclose the three/other references to Howell
    - Street, Alice -- May 9, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 35-g)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet Thanks for your letter./My trouble is that
    - Street, Alice -- May 12, 1923 (Box 8, Folder 35-h)
      12, Somerset Place, Bath Dear Violet Your letter of explanation/about Howell interested me
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Sept. 20, 1887-August 8, 1888] (Box 8, Folder 36-39)
      56 letters and fragments of letters to Violet Hunt.
      157 ll. + 24 envelopes
      With envelope dated July 6, 1889.
      With cigarette box with note.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Friday (Box 8, Folder 36-a)
      Undated fragment to Violet Hunt
      Well darling I had not time/to write to you last night
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-b)
      ...it. I was so miserable I felt/as if I could not tear
      1 l. (signed)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-c)
      ...Oh good Lord! Esther brought/Mary in here this morning
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Thursday/Friday (Box 8, Folder 36-d)
      Well, darling I didn't ride/to Helmsby after all
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-e)
      ...in & he has begun talking
      2 ll. (signed)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-f)
      ...I was never so really/happy before! wouldn't/you have
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-g)
      ...day would come, dont you dear? I shall count
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-h)
      opened cigarette box:
    - Strickland, Eustace (continued) -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 36-h)
      from A boy at Eton "Euty"
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 37-a)
      ALS to Violet Hunt.
      Dearest Violet It was so sweet of you my pet/coming down
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Tuesday [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 37-b)
      Dearest Violet. I was awfully sorry/to leave you
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Tuesday night [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 37-c)
      Dearest Violet. I don't know what/to think of myself!!
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 37-d)
      Dear Violet I have been ordered off home./Thanks very
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [n.d.] (Box 8, Folder 37-e)
      Darling. I believe I shall be able to/come to a ball
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Sept. 20, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-f)
      Dearest Violet. I felt so miserable at/having to leave
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Sept. 28, 1887?] (Box 8, Folder 37-g)
      Dearest Violet. Many happy returns of the/day, my own pet
      6 ll.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Sept. 29, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-h)
      Dearest Violet. Please forgive me for/writing so soon again,
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Sept. 30, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-i)
      Oh my darling. How sweet of you/how very sweet of you
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 3, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-j)
      Dearest Violet. How are you getting on/darling? Very well
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 7, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-k)
      Dearest Violet (my own Violet?) What a sweet long letter that
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 11, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-l)
      Darling Violet Oh! Violet, why darling do/you think I don't care
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 13 [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-m)
      Dearest Violet. I am going on where I left/off this evening,
      6 ll. + envelope
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Oct. 19, 1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-n)
      Dearest, dearest Violet. I felt so miserable when you/had to go
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 22, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-o)
      Dearest Violet. You old darling what a sweet/letter you wrote me
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Oct. 25, 1887] (Box 8, Folder 37-p)
      Darling old Violet. Thank you so much for sending/me the two
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 28, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-a)
      Darling old Violet. I was awfully disappointed at/not getting
      2 ll. (fragment) + envelope
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Oct. 30, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-b)
      Darling Violet. What a funny letter you wrote/me, two sheets
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Oct. 30, 1887?] (Box 8, Folder 38-c)
      Dearest dearest Vi (do you like that better than/Violet?) You
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 5, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-d)
      Dearest Violet. You dear old pet! how sweet the/drawings & hair
      2 ll. (fragment)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 9, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-e)
      Darling old Violet. You could not have rebuked me more/strongly
      8 ll. (with sketch)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 12, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-f)
      Dearest Violet. Thank you so much for your sweet letter which
      2 ll. (with sketch) + envelope
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 16, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-g)
      Darling Violet. You are utterly out of it about the sketch./I
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 21, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-h)
      Darling Violet. What a sweet letter you wrote me/today, I think
      4 ll. (with sketch)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Nov. 24, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-i)
      Dearest Vi I am just writing to tell you/that although
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Dec. 3, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-j)
      Dearest. What conclusions have I jumped to? tell/me & I will
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Dec. 10, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-k)
      Dearest Violet. My God. I don't know what/to think of myself
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Dec. 13, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-l)
      Dearest Violet Curse it! I dare hardly write for/fear
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Dec. 14, 1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-m)
      On Violet darling you have/made me so happy.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Dec. 20, 1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-n)
      Dearest Vio. I felt so miserable/at having to leave you
      3 ll. + envelope
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Dec. 21, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-o)
      Little Darling. How are you & did you get on all night/after
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Dec. 25, [1887] (Box 8, Folder 38-p)
      Dearest little Violet Thank you very much for the/X mas card but
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Jan. 5, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-a)
      Darling Thank you so much/for your letter,
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Jan. 21, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-b)
      Dearest Violet. You are an old darling for/forgiving me
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Jan. 24, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-c)
      Dearest Violet Thanks awfully for your/sweet letter.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Jan. 26, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-d)
      Dearest Violet Thanks awfully for your/little note,
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Jan. 30, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-e)
      Darling old pet. I am awfully sorry to hear that/you have
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Feb. 5, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-f)
      Dearest Violet. Thanks awfully for your/letter, I thought
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Feb. 13, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-g)
      Dearest Violet. I am awfully sorry/that I have left you
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Feb. 21, 1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-h)
      [envelope
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Feb. 23, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-i)
      Dearest Violet. I dont know how/to thank you enough
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Mar. 1, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-j)
      Dearest Violet. I hope you didn't get into/much of a row
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Mar. 9, 1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-k)
      Dearest V. I am staying out with/a ghastly headache.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Mar. 11, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-l)
      Dear V. Thanks awfully for paper. I feel better
      1 l. (postcard)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Mar. 16, 1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-m)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Apr. 6, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-n)
      Dear Violet. I have been meaning to/write to you for such
    - Strickland, Eustace -- Apr. 8, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-o)
      Dear Violet You simply heap coals of fire on/my head.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- May 16, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-p)
      Dear Violet. I am sorry you should/have had to wait
    - Strickland, Eustace -- May 27, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-q)
      Dear Violet. I am very very sorry/my last letter pained you.
    - Strickland, Eustace -- June 6, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-r)
      Dear Violet What an awful disappointment/I've had.
    - Strickland, Eustace (continued) -- June 6, [1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-r)
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [Aug. 8, 1888] (Box 8, Folder 39-s)
      Dearest Violet. I suppose you/think I have been a long
    - Strickland, Eustace -- [July 6, 1889] (Box 8, Folder 39-t)
    - Thirkell, Angela Mackail, 1890-1961. -- Sept. 21, 1932 (Box 8, Folder 40)
      6 Pembroke Gardens, W.8 Dear Violet - Thank you very much/for your letter
    - Toynbee, W. -- Dec. 28, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      Bromley, Kent Dear Mrs Hueffer, Many thanks for your "token,"
    - Troubridge, Una Vincenzo, Lady, 1887-1963. -- June 2, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 2-a)
      37, Holland Street, Kensington, W.8 Dear Violet. just a line/for John as she is tired
      2 l.
      With map drawn by Violet Hunt on inside pages.
    - Troubridge, Una Vincenzo, Lady, 1887-1963. -- Apr. 4, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 2-b)
      Marseille am having a lovely/lazy summer time here.
    - Turner, Juliette E. M. -- Oct. 16, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 3)
      16, Chelsea Embarkment, S.W. So many thanks for very interesting
    - Urstins, E. H. -- Feb. 28, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 4)
      Dunsfold House, Godalming Dear Violet, I have received your/letter of the 24th
    - Urstins, E. H. (continued) -- Feb. 28, 1905 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Valerie -- Nov. 27 [n.y.] (Box 9, Folder 5-a)
      Brazil All good/wishes for Xmas
      Signed "Jack & Valerie."
    - Valerie -- May 17, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 5-b)
      Tunis I am finding/ this country/most interesting.
    - Wahl, Arthur -- [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 6)
      1 Holly Place Dear Violet So Disappointed/that I couldnt make
    - Watts-Dunton, Theodore, 1832-1914. -- Apr. 25, 1901 (Box 9, Folder 7)
      2, The Pines, Putney Hill, S.W. Dear Miss Hunt, It would give me/the greatest pleasure
    - Waugh, Alec, 1898- -- Sept. 4, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 8)
      Chagford, Devon Dear Violet - I was very touched at your writing/to me
    - Waugh, Arthur, 1866-1943. -- Oct. 11, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 9-a-b)
      14A, Hampstead Lane, Highgate, N.6 Dear Miss Hunt: So many thanks for your kind/letters,
      1 l. + 1.
      With draft of letter by Violet Hunt to Mr. Waugh.
    - Waugh, Evelyn, 1903-1966. -- [Oct. 12, 1932] (Box 9, Folder 10)
      Savile Club, 69, Brook Street, W.1 Dear Miss Hunt Many thanks for/your letter & the enclosure
    - Wells, Catherine, 1872-1927. -- Saturday [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 11-a)
      Easton Glebe, Dunmow My poor dear Violet I've only been very very/busy.
    - Wells, Catherine, 1872-1927. -- Sept. 14 [1921] (Box 9, Folder 11-b)
      Easton Glebe, Dunmow Dear Violet. I am so sorry your letter/has had to wait.
      Jane Wells was H. G. Wells's second wife.
    - Wells, H. G. (Herbert George), 1866-1946. -- [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 12)
      ALS to [Violet Hunt]
      52, St. James's Court, Buckingham Gate, S.W.1 Rebecca is much better./She will be "at home"
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- -- [Oct. 7, 1918] (Box 9, Folder 13-a)
      [n.p.] Darling. I love you but I will never NEVER
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- -- [Feb. 12, 1919] (Box 9, Folder 13-b)
      Southcliffe Your letter was forwarded to Weymouth.
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- -- [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 13-c)
      Green Lanes, Redruth Dear Violet Alas! A poisoned snatch on my jaw mishandled
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- -- [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 13-d)
      ALS [init.] to Violet Hunt
      Hunstanton-on-Sea Dear Violet I went down & stayed with Lady Scott at Irving
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- -- [1916-1917] (Box 9, Folder 13-e)
      3 Crescent Avenue, Whitby My dear old Violet (You called me "dear old Rebecca
    - West, Rebecca, Dame, 1892- (Box 9, Folder 13-f)
      [September 9, 1924] Salzburg A Lovely place - but it rains/and rains
    - Williamson, George Charles, 1858-1942. -- Aug. 29, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      Hampstead, London Dear Mrs. Hueffer, It seems to me that you are surely right.
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- Jan. 1, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 15-a)
      25, Heath Drive, Hampstead, N.W.3 My dear Violet, The best of all good/wishes for Health,
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- Jan. 20, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 15-b)
      25, Heath Drive, Hampstead, N.W.3 My dear Violet, Forgive my delay/in replying
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- Jan. 29, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 15-c)
      [n.p.] My dear Violet, Thanks. I/have written
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- May 24, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 15-d)
      25, Heath Drive, Hampstead, N.W.3 My dear Violet, Hurrah for the great Moon!
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- Feb. 3, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 15-e)
      A [aman.] LS to Violet Hunt
      25, Heath Drive, Hampstead, N.W.3 My dear Violet- I am more sorry than/I can tell you
      In the hand of Lois Wise.
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. -- Feb. 5, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 15-f)
      25, Heath Drive, Hampstead, N.W.3 My dear Violet, I have found the ms. You
    - Wise, Thomas James, 1859-1937. (continued) -- Feb. 5, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 15-f)
      The photograph of Swinburne's epitaph for Charles Augustus Howell, enclosed with the letter, is now housed in Box 19, Folder 66.
    - Woolf, Virginia, 1882-1941. -- Oct. 7 [1932] (Box 9, Folder 16)
      52, Tavistock Square, W.C.1 Dear Miss Hunt, I am ashamed that I/have not written
    - Allingham, Helen -- May 7, 1924; n.d. (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Apperly, Mary -- Feb. 19, 1916 (Box 24, Folder 8)
      "Elvet Hill" by Mary Apperly, 1913
    - Freemantle, W.J. -- May 9, 1923-October 20, 1923 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Graham, R. B. -- Oct. 23, 1912 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Hawkins, Anthony -- Aug. 2, 1894-Dec. 7, 1910 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Hueffer, Ford M. -- [Oct. 1910-Feb. 1911] (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Megroz, R. L. -- Mar. 23, n.y. (Box 24, Folder 13-a)
    - Odgers, Blake -- Nove. 3, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 13-b)
    - Rae, Margaret -- Apr. 8, 1923-June 15, 1924 (Box 24, Folder 14-a-d)
    - Waugh, Mrs. Evelyn -- Feb. 27, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 15-a)
    - Waugh, Evelyn -- Feb. 29, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 15-b)
    - Williamson, Georg -- Jan. 1, 1930 (Box 24, Folder 15-c)
    - Willett, B. W. -- Jan. 21, 1932 (Box 24, Folder 15-d)
    - Wise, Thomas J. -- Apr. 16, 1930-July 4, 1931 (Box 24, Folder 15-e-h)
      Notes by Violet Hunt
    - TS carbons of letters: E. H. Ursinus, unidentified envelope, A. Orr, C. H. Keary, W. & S. Benson, C., H. H. Johnston, Constance, Merle Colby -- 1902 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 4. By Ford Madox Ford
    - Ford, Ford Madox, 1873-1939. -- Nov. 21, 1922 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      Paris Dear Violet. I was very sorry not to/be able to ring up again
      With envelope, addressed to Mrs. Hueffer. Envelope has Hunt's notation: "Ford's last letter to me. 1922".
  - 5. To Ford Madox Ford
    - [?] -- [Jan. 12, 1913] (Box 9, Folder 18)
      AL [postcard] to Ford Madox Ford
      Rome I have caught the/Poet & find him
      Possibly referring to Ezra Pound.
    - Brown, Ford Madox, 1821-1893. -- Apr. 21, 1880 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      ALS to Ford Madox Ford
      Manchester My Dear Ford, I hope you are/not cross with me
    - Denom, Hugh -- Oct. 25 [n.y.] (Box 9, Folder 20)
      St. Peter's, Edinburgh Dear Mr Hueffer, Of course I shall be delighted
    - Galsworthy, John, 1867-1933. -- Nov. 14, 1909 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      14, Addison Road, W. My dear Hueffer Well, well! I'm loth [sic] to think
      With envelope with note written on it, signed "V H".
    - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- Dec. 31, 1898 (Box 9, Folder 22-a)
      27 West Hill, Highgate Dear Ford Re: Duncan I received your long letter
    - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- Jan. 1, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 22-b)
      27 West Hill, Highgate Dear Ford Oliver I am sending you a formal letter
    - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- Jan. 12, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 22-c)
      27 West Hill, Highgate Dear Ford Duncan The enclosed copy correspondence
      The copy correspondence mentioned in
      Granett's letter is filed under Clark and MacDonald.
    - Garnett, Richard, 1835-1906. -- Jan. 12, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 22-d)
      Highgate Dear Ford yourself & Oliver When Macdonald and Oliver himself
    - Goesen, Maria -- Donnerstag Morgan [n.d.] (Box 9, Folder 23-a)
      [n.p.] Lieber Ford Ich bedaure von/Herzen
      With envelope with notes written in Violet Hunt's hand.
      Maria (Mimi) Goesen was Ford's cousin.
    - Goesen, Maria -- Aug. 23, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 23-b)
      Boppard Lieber Ford. Eber bekomme ich Deinen Brief
    - Goesen, Maria -- Nov. 16, 1910 (Box 9, Folder 23-c)
      Boppard Lieber Ford. Von meiner sehr schoenen Reise
    - Goesen, Maria -- Aug. 10, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 23-d-e)
      Boppard Lieber Ford. Ich muss Dich schnell
    - Haymarket Theatre, S.W. (London) -- July 26, 1912 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      Haymarket Theatre, S.W. Dear Sir I have just reced with the greatest/delight
      Written and signed by E. Lyall Swete.
    - Heron-Allen, Edward, 1861-1943. -- Jan. 2, 1914 (Box 9, Folder 25)
      33, Hamilton Terrace, N.W. Sir Whoever has conveyed to you the/impression
    - James, William, 1842-1910. -- Aug. 22, 1906 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Cambridge, MA My dear Sir, I got yours of the 17th/on my return
    - MacKenzie, Compton, Sir, 1883-1972. -- [Sept. 20] [n.y.] (Box 9, Folder 27)
      5 John St., Adelphi My dear Ford. Thanks awfully for your proposal which I appreciate
    - Patmore, Brigit -- [Apr. 21, 1914] (Box 9, Folder 28)
      AL [postcard] S to Ford Madox Ford
      With photograph of Brigit Patmore's sons on the front.
      With note in Violet Hunt's hand written at top.
    - Swete, E. Lyall -- Feb. 6, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Swete, E. Lyall (continued) -- Feb. 6, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      New York Dear Captain Ford Madox Hueffer How nice to write that Captain and to know
    - Synett, Netta -- Nov. 17, 1920 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      170, Buckingham Palace Roda, S.W. Dear Mr. Hueffer, Thank you for your letter.
  - 6. By and to others (by author, then by date)
    - Campbell, James -- Feb. 11, 1858 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      Brunswick Sq., Rinkdale My dear Mr. Greenwell My father has sent you
    - Clark & Macdonald -- Jan. 6, 1899 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      AL [copy] to R.S. Garnett
      Edinburgh Dear Sir, Duncan & Hueffer/We are this morning favoured with yours of 4th
      With copies of the following letters: L.W. Laurotte to Claggett Brachi, January 9, 1899; R.W. Noakes to R.S. Garnett, January 8, 1899; Chas. Clayton to Garnett, January 10, 1899; R.S. Garnett to Clark & Macdonald, January 7, 1899; Clark & Macdonald to R.S. Garnett, January 10, 1899; R.S. Garnett to Clark & Macdonald, January 10, 1899.
      Concerned with the affairs of Oliver Hueffer, Ford Madox Ford's brother.
    - City Coroner's Office (London) -- July 15, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      TL [copy] to Mrs. Shilton
      London Dear Madam, I regret that pressure of work
      Written and signed by F. J. Waldo.
    - City Coroner's Office (London) (continued) -- July 15, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      Concerns death of Mrs. Rossetti and a request by Hunt.
    - Coghill, H. A. -- Sept. 4, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      ALS to Miss Dodd
      Castletownshead Dear Miss Dodd It was very kind of you/to write
      The photograph of Mr. & Mrs. A. C. Coghill which was enclosed with this letter is now housed in Box 19, Folder 35.
      With newspaper photograph of Mr. & Mrs. Nevill Coghill.